<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Awards on CONAMEX International</title>
    <link>/awards/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Awards on CONAMEX International</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/awards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1995</title>
      <link>/awards/1995/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/awards/1995/</guid>
      <description>Accpac Development Partner of the Year August 21 - Orlando, FL
&amp;ldquo;Conamex’s president and head of software development, took the main stage today to receive the Accpac Development Partner of the Year 1995 as the Computer Associates CA World event held in Orlando ,Florida. On stage, Mr. L’Esperance was not only the recipient of the plaque but also received a specially emblazoned Computer Associates leather jacket to commemorate the award win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1999</title>
      <link>/awards/1999/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/awards/1999/</guid>
      <description>Accpac Development Partner of the Year ACCPAC Clients Cut Costs, Improve Cash Flow Management With Electronic Funds
September 28 - Pleasanton, CA
ACCPAC International, Inc., a business unit of Computer Associates International Inc. (NYSE: CA) interBiz Solutions division, announced today that it has acquired the entire EFT Direct series from Conamex International. The EFT solutions are available immediately for ACCPAC products including ACCPAC(R) Corporate Series(TM), ACCPAC(R) Small Business Series(TM), ACCPAC Plus(TM) Accounting and Simply Accounting(R).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2004</title>
      <link>/awards/2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/awards/2004/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Customer Experience Award &amp;amp; Networking Infrastructure Solution of the Year Finalist </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2005</title>
      <link>/awards/2005/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/awards/2005/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Impact Awards Winner – Security Solution of the Year The winning solutions included a biomarker study program written in VBA, for use in the biopharmaceutical industry. It provided a step by step process for lab technicians that also produced quantitative analysis, reports, mappings and highlighted specific data that needed attention from lab technicians. This new system created an unexpected and immense improvement in efficiencies, centralized data storage, retrieval and processing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2006</title>
      <link>/awards/2006/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/awards/2006/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Licensing Solutions Technology Innovation Partner of The Year news.microsoft.com - Partner of the Year Award Winners Announced
&amp;ldquo;Microsoft Corp. today announced the winners of the 2006 Microsoft Partner of the Year Awards. The awards recognize Microsoft Registered, Certified and Gold Certified partners that delivered exemplary solutions for their customers during the past year. Award winners were chosen from a group of finalists from around the world. Winners were announced at Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Worldwide Partner Conference 2006, the company&amp;rsquo;s premier annual event for industry partners, held this year in Boston.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2007</title>
      <link>/awards/2007/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/awards/2007/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Impact Awards Software Asset Management Solution of the Year Microsoft Impact Awards Small Business Specialist of the Year CDN Channel Elite Awards GOLD Winner Triple Crown for Conamex International as they capture Gold at the CEA Awards
November 15, 2007 - Toronto, ON
Montreal-based Conamex International announced today that it has won gold in the Best Small Business Solution category at the fifth annual Channel Elite Awards. This award caps wins for both Software Asset Management Solution of the Year and Small Business Specialist of the Year categories at the 2007 Microsoft Partner Program IMPACT Awards exactly one week ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2009</title>
      <link>/awards/2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/awards/2009/</guid>
      <description>CDN Channel Elite Awards Solution Provider of the Year Winner CDN Channel Elite Awards Best Small Business Solution of the Year Finalist Microsoft Impact Awards Small Business Specialist of the Year Finalist </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2010</title>
      <link>/awards/2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/awards/2010/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Impact Awards Small Business Specialist of the Year Winner Using Microsoft technologies, Conamex developed a custom software solution called Snowpro, which automates and integrates member, financial, store front, insurance and course management processes within a single system.
The management software solution is run out of the CSIA office, which then manages the systems for the other two associations. The solution is currently being used by tens of thousands of students, teachers and coaches, in conjunction with over 350 ski schools across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2011</title>
      <link>/awards/2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/awards/2011/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Impact Awards Small Business Specialist of the Year Finalist </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>